Guide to the Epsilon Sigma Phi, Alpha Omicron Chapter Records, 1912-2015 00278
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
Epsilon Sigma Phi, Alpha Omicron Chapter records
1912-2015
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
00278
4.16 Linear Feet (4 containers)
This collection documents the Cooperative Extension professional organization, Epsilon Sigma Phi, at Pennsylvania State University. The collection contains the constitution and bylaws, minutes, correspondence, agendas, committee member lists, and documentation on awards granted by the organization.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for use only by verified members of the fraternity and/or researchers with written permission of the fraternity/sorority.
For information on accessing this collection please contact the Special Collections Research Services Unit at ul-spcolref@lists.psu.edu.
Biographical or Historical Note
Epsilon Sigma Phi, Alpha Omicron chapter, is a Cooperative Extension professional's organization. The Cooperative Extension System is a nationwide, non-credit educational network. Membership in Epsilon Sigma Phi, Alpha Omicron chapter is open to full-time faculty, professional, and administrative staff who have exhibited excellence in education and programming leadership and who have held part-time Extension appointments for at least two years.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the Cooperative Extension professional organization, Epsilon Sigma Phi, at Pennsylvania State University. The collection contains the constitution and bylaws, minutes, correspondence, agendas, committee member lists, and documentation on awards granted by the organization.
Audio
- Activities, 1937-1954 (Box 3)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted: Yes
- Alpha Omicron Award Program, 2000 (Box 3)
- Alpha Omicron Chapter: Constitution and Bylaws, 1936-1973 (Box 2)
- Alpha Omicron Chapter: Meeting Agendas, Annual, 1968-1975 (Box 2)
- Alpha Omicron Chapter: Membership Transfer, 1966 (Box 2)
- Alpha Omicron Meeting Minutes and Committee Reports, 1990/03 (Box 3)
- Alpha Omicron Newsletter, 1989-2003 (Box 3)
- Annalist's Records: Adams to Duvall, 1912-1981 (Box 4)
- Annalist's Records: Eakin to Irwin, 1912-1981 (Box 4)
- Annalist's Records: Jackson to Michael, 1912-1981 (Box 4)
- Annalist's Records: Miller to Rugh, 1912-1981 (Box 4)
- Annalist's Records: Sammons to Zundel, 1912-1981 (Box 4)
- Annalists Reports, 1949-1975 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee, 1990-2000 (Box 3)
- Awards (listing and information), 1977-1997 (Box 3)
- Business correspondence, 1973 (Box 2)
- Business Information, 1950-1954 (Box 2)
- Bylaws, Undated (Box 3)
- Chapter Awards and Recognition, 1999-2001 (Box 3)
- Charter Members, 1930 (Box 2)
- Civil Service Retirement Major Changes, 1971 (Box 2)
- Committee Members Lists, 1968-1977 (Box 2)
- Committee Members Lists, 1986-1989 (Box 1)
- Committee Reports, 1970-1976 (Box 2)
- Committees, 1990-2003 (Box 3)
- Conference, 1982/11 (Box 1)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 1966/06 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1938-1955 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1964-1974 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1974 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1983-2002 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 1)
- Correspondence and Reports, 1953-1958 (Box 3)
- Correspondence (letters), 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Correspondence (fiscal), 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Correspondence (mailed), 1986 (Box 1)
- Correspondence (within State), 1988-1989 (Box 1)
- Distinguished Ruby Award, Undated (Box 2)
- Distinguished Ruby Award - Biographical Sketch Information, Undated (Box 2)
- Distinguished Ruby Award - Certificate of Recognition, 1936-1955 (Box 2)
- Duties of Committees, 1962 (Box 2)
- Extension Extended, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
- Extension Tour Slide Show, 1985 (Box 4)
- Finance Committee, 1995-2002 (Box 3)
- Financial Information, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
- Goals and Recommendations, 1990/03 (Box 3)
- Grand Council Annual Meeting Reports, 1936-1972 (Box 2)
- Grand Council Meeting - Memorial Service Forms, 1964-1974 (Box 2)
- Grand Officers Secretary and Treasurers correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 2)
- Historical Information, 1930-1935 (Box 2)
- Historical Information, 1940-1947 (Box 2)
- History, 1927-1969 (Box 2)
- International, 1997 (Box 3)
- Invitation Ceremony, 1972 (Box 2)
- Keys and Insignia, Undated (Box 2)
- Lawrence County Extension Staff photo, undated (Box 4)
- Listserv, 2000 (Box 3)
- Loan and Fellowship Fund, 1976-1981 (Box 1)
- Loan and Fellowship Fund, 1977-1981 (Box 3)
- Meeting, Annual and Banquet, 1996-1998 (Box 3)
- Meeting, Annual (pamphlets), 1986-2002 (Box 3)
- Meeting Minutes, 1966-1981 (Box 2)
- Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
- Meeting Minutes and Treasurers Report, 1960-1982 (Box 1)
- Meeting Minutes, Annual, 1982-1985 (Box 1)
- Meeting Minutes (notebook), 1927-1964 (Box 1)
- Members List - Active, 1955-1981 (Box 2)
- Members List - Active/Retired, 1988 (Box 1)
- Members, New, 1964-1975 (Box 2)
- Membership and Initiation Committee, 1979-1990 (Box 3)
- Membership Information, 1951-1957 (Box 3)
- Membership Information and Reports, 1996-2001 (Box 3)
- Membership - Life Active, 1989 (Box 1)
- Membership List, Association, 1938-1976 (Box 2)
- Membership Lists, 1983-1986 (Box 1)
- Membership Transfer Application Forms, 1965 (Box 2)
- Mixer, College of Agriculture Service Newsletter, 1966-1982 (Box 4)
- Mixer Newsletter, 1970-1974 (Box 2)
- National and Regional Awards Committee, Undated (Box 3)
- National Association of County Agricultural Agents Group Photos, 1959-2001 (Box 4)
- National Chapter - Constitution and Bylaws, 1933-1970 (Box 2)
- National District Service Ruby Award, 1995 (Box 3)
- National Epsilon Sigma Phi Yearbooks & Constitution & By-Laws, 1947-2015 (Box 4)
- National Foundation, 1989 (Box 3)
- National Newsletter, 1980-2002 (Box 3)
- National Officers Duties, Undated (Box 2)
- National Past Officers (permanent), 1968-1975 (Box 2)
- National Retirement correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 2)
- National Scholarship Loans, Undated (Box 2)
- Newsletters, 1977-1989 (Box 1)
- Officers, Local Chapter, 1943-1978 (Box 2)
- Pendants and Pins Order Form, 1977/01 (Box 2)
- Pennsylvania Association of County Agricultural Agents Code of Ethics poster, 1955 (Box 4)
- Pennsylvania JCEP BEPA Galaxy Conference, 1997/05/14 (Box 3)
- Professional Improvement, 1950 (Box 2)
- Project Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 2)
- Regional Mid-Center Award, 1994 (Box 3)
- Resignation Letters, 1974-1985 (Box 2)
- Retiree Insurance, 1971 (Box 2)
- Retirees Newsletter, 1969-2003 (Box 3)
- Scholarship Recipients, 1970-1979 (Box 2)
- Scholarships and Loans Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 3)
- Secretary - Treasurer Duties, Undated (Box 2)
- Song Sheets, Undated (Box 2)
- Sympathy and Memorial, 1988-1991 (Box 3)
- Sympathy Cards, Undated (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Notebook, 1930-1958 (Box 1)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1990/03 (Box 3)
- Untitled, Undated; Audio Cassette Standard (Box 1)
- Yearbook, 1932-1960 (Box 1)